Lifeforce Transfer has ended!
Is it true that Elymas
is living it up in Rondalm?
I'm not certain,
but I've heard someone very similar to him
has achieved exceptional success there.
You don't waste time. Bring it on!
Rampart
Reflection
Rampart Reflection!
Shield Bash!
He must be using his family name
to blackmail a guild employee!
How dare he tarnish the Edvaughn
name after leaving this place?
There's no familial love
between us anymore, Elymas.
Lord Elymas is an intelligent
and principled man.
I can't imagine he'd
strong-arm anyone like that.
We should verify
the truth first, Lord Aizas.
In that case, Thomas, you go do it.
If he really is using the family name,
have him removed from the guild's roster
and ban him from re-registering.
And tell him...
If he does anything like this again,
he's a dead man.
It's me, my lord.
Ah, Malice. Come in.
You needn't be so formal, Malice.
You're the future head
of the family. You're my heir.
You could even call me Father.
Regarding your discussion,
you're too soft on him.
Thomas favors Elymas too much,
and removing him from
the guild roster isn't enough.
When Elymas loses his means
of supporting himself,
he'll become desperate
and commit more folly.
If he becomes a bandit,
he'll be a massive stain
on the Edvaughn family name.
You're absolutely right,
but what are you trying to say, Malice?
You and I should go see what he's up to...
and deal with him directly.
Thanks for waiting.
Hey.
I'm glad you got
the skillbook you wanted.
Loading
Begin Adventure
Episode 11\h\h\h\hInescapable Past
I actually bought
the Fang of Smoldering Insanity.
It's fine. I said you could.
It's a gift.
You bought me that
Ironpiercer, didn't you?
That was way less expensive.
Besides, we needed that
to slay Golden Raana.
I knew I'd make back what I spent.
And you won't with that skill tree?
No, I will. You can be sure of that.
Fang of Smoldering Insanity skillbook.
Fang of Smoldering Insanity Skillbook
Market Price: 30,000,000G
Unlocks Fang of Smoldering Insanity skill tree.
Beware of those with this skill tree. Dragging
his shattered body and letting his torn tail flutter,
not even the God of Death dares approach his
unstoppable rampage.
Market price: 30,000,000 gold.
Beware of those with this skill tree.
Dragging his shattered body
and letting his torn tail flutter,
not even the God of Death dares
approach his unstoppable rampage.
Um, Ruche, would it be okay
if I used it now?
I'm worried someone might steal it.
Of course. Please, go right ahead.
But is it actually strong?
What?
Fang of Smoldering Insanity.
The descriptive text makes me
a little uneasy, but it's safe, right?
It doesn't have any
weird drawbacks, does it?
It's definitely strong.
With enough skill points,
it'll really start to shine.
Fang of Smoldering Insanity gives suicidal
combat skills for those prepared to die.
Combining it with the Heavy Knight class
raises its firepower to absurd levels.
Here goes.
Gulp.
Gulp
Skill Trees: Heavy Knight
Remaining Skill Points: 13
I'll overwrite Defense Booster
with Fang of Smoldering Insanity.
Skill Trees: Heavy Knight
Remaining Skill Points: 13
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Defense Booster
Beginner Swordsmanship
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Fang of Smoldering Insanity
A-All right! Fang of Smoldering
Insanity is finally mine!
Skill Trees: Heavy Knight
Remaining Skill Points: 13
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Fang of Smoldering Insanity
Beginner Swordsmanship
Look, Ruche! I got this because of you!
Didn't you say we shouldn't
show our stats to others?
But I'm starting to feel happy, too.
Are you going to put points into it now?
No. First, I'll put points in Oath
of the Heavy Armor to grab this skill...
We've gained a lot of levels, so we
should probably straighten out my gear.
Then why don't we go
for dungeon drops?
What?
Listen, Ruche, targeting
specific item drops...
Previous Drops
isn't out of the question.
All right!
You liked my idea!
Who's that?
Idiot, that's the local lord!
What?!
That's the Master Swordsman.
Why, if it isn't Count Edvaughn.
What brings you to our
humble Adventurer's Guild?
I have something important
to discuss. Clear the room.
Uh, excuse me?
Why don't we speak in the back?
Did you not hear me? Clear the room.
Th-The guild is closed for the day!
I don't know why he's here,
but I'd like to avoid Aizas.
Adventurers, please leave
the building quickly!
He probably feels the same way.
Let's go, Ruche.
We don't want his attention.
O-Okay.
That's Lord Aizas, isn't it?
I didn't have a good impression of
the Edvaughn family to begin with,
but he seems overbearing and nasty.
You there, adventurer. You stay.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I was just trying to lighten
the mood by clowning around!
Don't worry, Ruche.
He's not interested in you.
It seems he has business with me.
What say we team up this time?
What does a noble want with me?
How dare you speak to me like that?
Mr. Elymas, you should be more respectful!
Come on, let's apologize!
You.
You're awfully friendly with Elymas.
What are you to him?
Huh?
Y-You know Mr. Elymas?
Ruche, go outside.
This is my problem.
B-But...
If I'm in the way, I'll leave.
But telling me I shouldn't get involved
just makes me want to stay.
Maybe there's nothing
I can do by being here.
Ruche.
But friends stand by each other
in times like these.
Not this time, Ruche.
I can't leave you
when you look so distraught.
You, a commoner,
dare to tell us what to do?
Leave at once!
Father.
Let's allow her to stay.
She and Elymas seem quite close.
She could be involved in the rumors.
Fine.
I promised I'd let you
deal with him anyway.
Count Edvaughn.
Did you hear about this promising man
and come to recruit him
to your private army?
The news reached you quickly.
This adventurer is courteous and brave.
His name will go down
in this guild's history.
Guildmaster.
Drop the obvious act.
You already know, don't you?
What?
This man is an Edvaughn!
What?!
Wh-What do you mean?
One of your guild employees
must be conspiring with this brat.
What?!
Find them all and bring
them here this instant!
W-Wait. That can't be...
R-Right away, sir!
Mr. Elymas, is Count Aizas...
He's my father.
I hate to say it, but it's true.
You're an embarrassment
to the Edvaughn family.
I merely exiled you because I believed
you wouldn't do anything stupid.
Elymas, have you forgotten what I said?
If you used the Edvaughn
family name again,
I said I'd have your head!
I've been enjoying too much success
since leaving the count's family.
Aizas came to check on me
because he suspects I cheated my way
into my unusual promotion.
So that's why you're here.
I haven't been using the family name.
Th-That's right.
Why are you so distrustful of him?
It's impossible. It can't be done.
In just one week,
a single adventurer couldn't
possibly slay a level 50 Dreamlord.
Father, our goal this time
is to investigate.
There's no need to rush.
What?
Elymas, I hear you're around level 40.
That's perfect. I just finished using
Lifeforce Transfer to reach level 45.
We can verify your story
with a practice fight.
Lifeforce Transfer.
She's been farming EXP
by killing high-level criminals.
It's barbaric.
If we're around the same level, his combat
experience should give him the edge.
We need only cross blades briefly
to determine the truth.
Don't be ridiculous, Malice.
Even if your levels are comparable,
a fight between a Master Swordsman
and Heavy Knight is a joke.
It's just practice, Father.
And isn't it impressive that he rose
this far this quickly by himself?
I was just hoping to learn from him.
Of course, if he's lying...
then this practice could also
be his punishment.
Master Swordsman is a powerful class.
Its Attack and Speed are insanely high,
and many of its skills
are straightforward and brutal.
Without high Attack or Speed,
the Heavy Knight is stuck defending
against a Master Swordsman.
Even if I land a hit,
it won't end the fight.
I can probably put up a bit of a fight,
but I doubt she'll let it go at that.
This is nonsense.
Why are you so interested
in Elymas, Malice?
I chose you to be my—
Fine. I accept your mock battle.
But I have one condition.
If you acknowledge my power,
never concern yourself with me again.
You brat!
I'm delighted, Elymas.
That's what I like to hear.
Mr. Elymas, this is crazy.
It goes without saying,
but don't kill him, Malice.
This is my chance
to demonstrate my integrity.
No, with this duel, I'll say
goodbye to the Edvaughn family.
Nice single-edged sword, Malice.
The Magiblade Watercrow.
It provides a significant boost to Attack.
All she has to do is wildly swing it
around to be a serious threat.
Father secretly acquired this
so he could give it to you.
We haven't practiced since we were little.
To be honest, I didn't think
you hated me this much.
Parry!
Sh-She's so fast!
I'm relieved, Elymas. This will be fun.
After all...
this is the last time I'll play
with the man I looked up to.
I'll start by cutting off your left arm!
M-Mr. Elymas is being overpowered?
What's wrong? Come on!
Come on!
Elymas Edvaughn
Elymas is being a stubborn fool.
Malice is toying with him.
Elymas Edvaughn
I've already lost about 40% of my HP.
Too slow. That's not quick enough to—
What?!
Vital Slice!
Vital Slice
H-He did it! He landed a direct hit!
A Master Swordsman and Heavy Knight's
stats are worlds apart!
Did Malice let her guard down?
The Heavy Knight's Attack is low,
but that should've hurt a bit.
But tricks like that will only work once.
Title: Upsetter
\h\h\hAttack and Speed increase by 15% when
\h\h\hfighting higher-level enemies.
The Upsetter's Speed boost
and a surprise Shadow Stomp
barely enabled me to land one hit.
Give me everything you've got, Malice.
It's not like you'll back down
after that, right?
I'm glad.
You're still you.
I was worried our time together
would end quickly!
As a token of respect
for landing a hit on me...
I'll show you a Master Swordsman skill.
Cold-As-Steel Cutter!
She vanished?!
Lightning-fast strikes are what
the Master Swordsman class is all about!
Did I manage to survive?
One more strike.
Mr. Elymas!
Translator:
Sho Stifler
Timer:
Krzysztof Kunc
Editor:
Salem Alabanza
Quality Control:
Gabriella Alabanza
Final Quality Control:
Sriram Gurunathan
My fierce battle against Malice continues.
The Master Swordsman's stat advantage
and brutal skills are no surprise.
No matter how many cheap tricks a Defense
specialist like the Heavy Knight uses,
he can't win.
Don't worry, Ruche.
I've got the Fang of Smoldering
Insanity we acquired together.
Next time, "Malice the Master Swordsman."
It's time to show off
the Heavy Knight's evolution!